<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="103">
	<author>Glowins Modschmiede</author>
	<version>3.0.0.2</version>
	<contributors>Agrarplay und LU Wohnzimmer, Funjetor</contributors >

	<title>
		<en>Headland Management</en>
		<de>Vorgewende Management</de>
		<fr>Gestion Des Fourrières</fr>
    </title>
    <description>
		<en>
<![CDATA[
Headland management for tractors, field sprayers, mowers and harvesters

Description:
Headland management allows functions to be combined in the vehicle and activated together at the touch of a button to simplify turning manoeuvres during field work. All functions can be activated and deactivated individually for each vehicle via a GUI in order to achieve ideal adaptation to the work being carried out.

Headland management must be added to the respective vehicle as a one-off configuration in the shop or in the workshop before use. The cost for this is 3000$. 
It can be activated and deactivated in the vehicle. Various buttons can also be configured for activation and deactivation.

Functions included:
- Reduce speed (cruise control) and raise again, reactivate cruise control if it was previously active
- Raise lowered implements and lower them again, optionally raise front implements before raising rear implements
- Turn the plough, single-stage or two-stage (via the centre position)
- Raise and change track markers
- Change sides with crab steering activated
- Switch off PTO shaft(s) and hydraulics and switch on again
- Warning tone when headland mode is activated
- On/off switch: The headland management can be switched on and off. This prevents accidental activation during transfer to the work site and improves road safety.
- Automatic headland management: Automatic activation of headland mode when the headland is reached. Optional return to field mode after completing the 180° turn.
- Option to temporarily deactivate headland automatic headland by pressing a button
- Contour guidance: Automatic control along the field boundary or along the cultivated area
- The configuration is saved and restored for each device type 

With existing EnhancedVehicle (FS25_EnhancedVehicle):
- Deactivate and reactivate GPS lane guidance, optionally trigger the turning function
- Release and reset active differential locks
- Use of EV headland detection if it has been activated

Pre-assigned key combinations (can be changed):
- Switch headland management on/off: (left) Shift + (left) Alt + X
- Switch operating mode (field mode / headland mode): (left) Shift + X
- Call up GUI for configuration: (left) Shift + (left) Ctrl + X

Other prepared key combinations (not pre-assigned)
- Temporarily deactivating/reactivating (toggling) the  headland automatic function
- Temporarily deactivating the automatic headland automatic function
- Reactivating the automatic automatic
- Activation of the field mode
- Activation of the headland mode

Change Log V3.0.0.1:
- Fixed a bug in the handling of actionEvents, which caused keyboard input to be partially ignored
- Availability in mission vehicles restored

Change Log V3.0.0.2:
- Availability in mission vehicles after loading the game

GitHub link: https://github.com/jason0611/FS25_HeadlandManagement
Further ideas or requests are welcome there
]]>
		</en>	
		<de>
<![CDATA[
Vorgewende-Management für Schlepper, Feldspritzen, Mäher und Erntemaschinen

Beschreibung:
Mit dem Vorgewende-Management können Funktionen im Fahrzeug zusammengefasst und gemeinsam per Knopfdruck aktiviert werden, um Wendemanöver bei der Feldarbeit zu vereinfachen. Alle Funktionen sind je Fahrzeug über eine GUI einzeln aktivierbar und deaktivierbar, um eine ideale Anpassung an die durchgeführten Arbeiten zu erreichen.

Das Vorgewende-Management muss vor der Nutzung im Shop oder in der Werkstatt dem jeweiligen Fahrzeug einmalig als Konfiguration hinzugefügt werden. Die Kosten dafür liegen bei 3000€. 
Es kann im Fahrzeug mit aktiviert und deaktiviert werden. Es lassen sich auch verschiedene Tasten für Aktivierung und Deaktivierung konfigurieren.

Enthaltene Funktionen:
- Geschwindigkeit (Tempomat) reduzieren und wieder anheben, Tempomat reaktivieren, falls er vorher aktiv war
- Abgesenkte Geräte ausheben und wieder absenken, optional Anheben der Frontanbaugeräte vor dem Anheben der Heckanbaugeräte
- Pflug drehen, einstufig oder zweistufig (über die Mittelstellung)
- Spurreisser ausheben und wechseln
- Seitenwechsel bei aktiviertem Hundegang
- Zapfwelle(n) und Hydraulik abschalten und wieder anschalten
- Hinweiston bei aktiviertem Vorgewendemanagement
- An/Aus-Schalter: Das Vorgewende Management kann an- und abgeschaltet werden. Dadurch wird versehentliches Auslösen beim Transfer zum Einsatzort vermieden und die Verkehrssicherheit verbessert.
- Vorgewendeautomatik: Automatische Aktivierung des Vorgewendemodus, wenn das Vorgewende erreicht wird. Wahlweise Rückkehr in den Feldmodus nach Abschluss der 180°-Wende.
- Option zur vorübergehenden Deaktivierung der Vorgewendeautomatik per Taste
- Konturführung: Automatische Steuerung entlang der Feldgrenze oder entlang der bearbeiteten Fläche
- Die Konfiguration wird pro Gerätetyp gespeichert und wiederhergestellt 

Hinweis: Bei aktivierter Konturführung sollte eine Arbeitsgeschwindigkeit von 10 km/h nicht überschritten werden, sonst kann es bei der Lenkung zu starkem Pendeln kommen. In diesem Fall generell einfach kurz die Geschwindigkeit reduzieren.
Die Parameter der Konturführung können über die Konsole mit dem Befehl "hlmParameter [smoothness] [sharpness]" angepasst werden. Angepasste Werte werden im modSettings-Verzeichnis gespeichert.

Bei vorhandenem EnhancedVehicle (FS25_EnhancedVehicle):
- GPS Spurführung deaktivieren und reaktivieren, wahlweise Auslösen der Wendefunktion
- Aktive Differentialsperren lösen und wieder setzen
- Nutzung der Vorgewendeerkennung von EV, wenn sie aktiviert wurde

Vorbelegte Tastenkombinationen (änderbar):
- Vorgewende Management an-/ausschalten: (links) Shift + (links) Alt + X
- Betriebsmodus umschalten (Feld-Modus / Vorgewende-Modus): (links) Shift + X
- GUI zur Konfiguration aufrufen: (links) Shift + (links) Strg + X

Weitere vorbereitete Tastenkombinationen (nicht vorbelegt)
- Vorübergehenden Deaktivierung/Reaktivierung (umschalten) der Vorgewendeautomatik
- Vorübergehende Deaktivierung der Vorgewendeautomatik
- Reaktivierung der Vorgewendeautomatik
- Aktivierung des Feldmodus
- Aktivierung des Vorgewendemodus

Change Log V3.0.0.1:
- Fehler im Umgang mit actionEvents behoben, wodurch Tastatureingaben teilweise ignoriert wurden
- Verfügbarkeit in Missionsfahrzeugen wiederhergestellt

Change Log V3.0.0.2:
- Verfügbarkeit in Missionsfahrzeugen auch bei geladenem Spielstand

GitHub-Link: https://github.com/jason0611/FS25_HeadlandManagement
Weitere Ideen oder Wünsche werden dort gerne entgegengenommen
]]>
		</de>
		<fr>
<![CDATA[
Gestion des fourrières pour les tracteurs, les pulvérisateurs, les faucheuses et les moissonneuses.

Description :
La gestion des fourrières permet de regrouper des fonctions dans le véhicule et de les activer ensemble en appuyant sur un bouton, afin de simplifier les manœuvres de demi-tour lors du travail dans les champs. Toutes les fonctions peuvent être activées et désactivées individuellement par véhicule via une GUI afin d'obtenir une adaptation idéale aux travaux effectués.

La gestion des manœuvres en bout de champ doit être ajoutée une seule fois à la configuration de chaque véhicule avant d'être utilisée dans la boutique ou à l'atelier. Le coût de cette opération est de 3000€. 
Il peut être activé et désactivé dans le véhicule. Il est également possible de configurer différents boutons pour l'activation et la désactivation.

Fonctions incluses :
- Réduire la vitesse (régulateur de vitesse) et la relever, réactiver le régulateur de vitesse s'il était actif auparavant.
- Relever et redescendre les outils abaissés, en option relever les outils avant avant de relever les outils arrière
- Tourner la charrue, à un ou deux niveaux (par la position centrale)
- Relevage et changement des traceurs
- Changement de côté avec la marche en crabe activée
- Débrayer la/les prise(s) de force et le système hydraulique et les réactiver
- Signal sonore lorsque la gestion des manœuvres en bout de champ est activée
- Interrupteur marche/arrêt : la gestion des fourrières peut être activée et désactivée. Cela permet d'éviter les déclenchements accidentels lors du transfert vers le lieu d'intervention et d'améliorer la sécurité routière.
- Automatisme de bout de champ : activation automatique du mode bout de champ lorsque la fourrière est atteinte. Retour facultatif au mode champ une fois le demi-tour à 180° terminé.
- Option de désactivation temporaire de l'automatisme des fourrières par touche.
- Guidage du contour : commande automatique le long de la limite du champ ou le long de la surface travaillée.
- La configuration est enregistrée et restaurée par type d'appareil. 

En présence d'un EnhancedVehicle (FS25_EnhancedVehicle) :
- Désactiver et réactiver le guidage GPS, déclencher au choix la fonction de demi-tour
- Débloquer et réactiver les blocages de différentiel actifs
- Utilisation de la détection des manœuvres en bout de champ de EV, si elle a été activée

Raccourcis clavier prédéfinis (modifiables) :
- Activer/désactiver la gestion des fourrières : (gauche) Shift + (gauche) Alt + X
- Commuter le mode de fonctionnement (mode champ / mode bout de champ) : (gauche) Shift + X
- Appeler l'interface graphique pour la configuration : (gauche) Shift + (gauche) Ctrl + X

Autres combinaisons de touches préparées (non prédéfinies)
- Désactivation/réactivation temporaire (commutation) de l'automatisme des manœuvres en bout de champ
- Désactivation temporaire de l'automatisme des manœuvres en bout de champ
- Réactivation de l'automatisme des fourrières
- Activation du mode champ
- Activation du mode fourrière

Change Log V3.0.0.1:
- Correction d'un bug dans la gestion des actionEvents, qui faisait que les saisies clavier étaient partiellement ignorées.
- Disponibilité rétablie dans les véhicules de mission

Change Log V3.0.0.2:
- Disponibilité dans les véhicules de mission même lorsque la sauvegarde du jeu est chargée

Lien GitHub : https://github.com/jason0611/FS25_HeadlandManagement
D'autres idées ou souhaits y sont les bienvenus, veuillez écrire en allemand ou en anglais
]]>
		</fr>
 	</description>	
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>
	<iconFilename>icon_HeadlandManagement.dds</iconFilename>
	<extraSourceFiles>
    	<sourceFile filename="headlandManagementRegister.lua" />
    </extraSourceFiles>
	<l10n filenamePrefix="l10n/l10n" />
	<actions>
		<action name="HLM_TOGGLESTATE" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="HLM_SWITCHOFF" categorie="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="HLM_SWITCHON" categorie="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="HLM_SHOWGUI" categorie="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="HLM_MAINSWITCH" categorie="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="HLM_TOGGLEAUTO" categorie="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="HLM_AUTOON" categorie="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="HLM_AUTOOFF" categorie="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
	</actions>
	<inputBinding>	
		<actionBinding action="HLM_TOGGLESTATE">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lshift KEY_x" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="HLM_SHOWGUI">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lshift KEY_lctrl KEY_x" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="HLM_MAINSWITCH">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lshift KEY_lalt KEY_x" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
	</inputBinding>
</modDesc>
